918-740-1775

Professional Summary

A National Scholar Computer Engineering and Computer Science student at USC with over four years of programming experience and nearly a year of experience working in a professional setting including working on internal IT applications and embedded set top box applications. A two year member of the USC Autonomous Underwater Vehicle team competing in the AUVSI RoboSub event.

Education

 University of Southern California—Los Angeles, CA Majoring in Computer Engineering and Computer Science

- University GPA: 3.5, Major GPA: 3.9

- Presidential Scholar

- Projected Graduation Date: May, 2014

Technical Summary

- Languages: C, C++, Java, Python, Verilog, Languages: C, C++, Languages: C, C++,
- Libraries/Frameworks: OpenGL, ROS (Robot Operating System), OpenCV, Berkeley Sockets
- Systems/Tools: Linux and Unix variants (Debian, Ubuntu, Solaris), OSX, Windows 2000/XP/Vista/7, SVN, Git, Mercurial, Eclipse, Trixbox (Asterisk based PBX), Apache, VMWare ESX, Multithreaded Environments (Using Agents), Maven

Professional Experience

• **DIRECTV**—El Segundo, CA Software Engineering Intern May 2012–August 2012

- Did embedded systems work with set top box UI in Java
- Created tool to increase productivity when working with set top box assets
- Nelson Auto Group—Tulsa, OK

Information Technology Intern May 2011–August 2011, December 2011–January 2012

- Created a system to effectively and efficiently keep copies of all physical media needed for the company's computer and technical systems.
- Created a system to allow managers to easily access recorded calls through a web interface using PHP to access Asterisk servers.

Relevant coursework

- In Progress: Computer Science 271—Discrete Mathematics
- In Progress: Electrical Engineering 450—Networking
- In Progress: Electrical Engineering 457—Computer System Organization
- Computer Science 201—Software Development
- Electrical Engineering 357—Computer Architecture
- Compuer Science 200—Object-Oriented Programming
- Computer Science 480—Computer Graphics
- Electrical Engineering 201—Introduction to Digital Circuits